toggle.com 2015-03-24

# Toggle - privacy policy

We use cookies to give you the best experience. If you continue, we'll assume you accept to receive all cookies from our website.[privacy policy](https://www.toggle.com/lv/privacy_policy/view.htm?lang=en) __

## PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA 

In compliance with Act 15/1999, 13 December, of Protection of Personal Information and development regulation, Bibado Investments S.L (hereinafter, the Company), information society service provider of the web portal TOGGLE, (hereinafter, the portal) informs you that the information obtained through the portal will be handled by the Company, as the party in charge of the File, with the goal of facilitating the requested services, attending to queries, carrying out statistical studies that will allow an improvement in service, carrying out typical administrative tasks, sending information that may result of your interest through bulletins and similar publications, as well as developing sales promotion and publicity activities related to the portal.

The user expressly authorizes the use of their electronic mail address and other means of electronic communication (e.g., mobile telephone) so that the Company may use said means of communication and for the development of informed purposes.

Upon providing your information, you declare to be familiar with the contents herein and expressly authorize the use of the data for the informed purposes. The user may revoke this consent at any time, without retroactive effects.

The Company commits to complying with its obligation as regards secrecy of personal information and its duty to process the information confidentially, and to take the necessary technical, organizational and security measures to avoid the altering, loss, and unauthorized handling or access of the information, in accordance with the rules established in the Protection of Personal Information Act and the applicable law.

The Company only obtains and retains the following information about visitors to our portal:

-a. The domain name of the Internet service provider (ISP) and/or the IP address that gives them access to the network.

–b. The date and time of access to our website.

-c. The internet address from which the link that that leads to our website originated.

–d. The type of browser client.

-e. The client’s operating system.

This information is anonymous, not being able to be associated with a specific, identified user.

The portal uses cookies, small information files generated on the user's computer, with the aim of obtaining the following information:

-a. The date and time of the most recent visit to our web page.

-b. Security control elements to restricted areas.

The user has the option of blocking cookies by means of selecting the corresponding option on their web browser. Some of our pages use a feature of your browser called a "cookie."A cookie is a small file stored on the user's computer containing information about the computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our portal. Some of our partners use cookies on our portal (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Please refer to their privacy policies of the network for details.

## Use of Personal Information

Any information you send will be held in the strictest confidence.

In no way, your personal information will be ever used without your consent.

To ensure this, all forms on our portal that send information to a database that will be used in the future (e.g. the newsletter list) have opt-in options, meaning you receive a confirmation email where you click a generated link specifying that you would like to receive information from us in the future.

If you do not confirm your subscription we will not add you to our database. Be assured that we do not sell our name and address lists.

If you choose to receive information from us, each message will also include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from future newsletters, if you wish to cancel.

The only information we automatically collect is that related to the use of our portal. This information is anonymous and is gathered through our servers log files.

These log files record generic information, such as the number of visits our portal receives, the types of browsers used and the number of files downloaded, but never personal information.

This log file information allows us to create better content aimed at our viewer's preferences.

## Use of Links

The portal contains links to external websites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such external websites.

We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of every external website that is linked from our portal.

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by the portal.

## Changes to this policy

The Company reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy from time to time.

We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes to be minor.

We will post any Privacy Policy changes on the portal.

## Ads on this site

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the portal.

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, read the information below:

-Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Portal.

-Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to the Portal, and other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## Contact us

The Company knows that your privacy is very important to you and we respect that.  
We welcome questions and comments regarding this policy, so feel free to contact us.

At any moment, the user may exercise the rights of access, rectification, cancellation or opposition by sending an email with the reference TOGGLE (Legal Department) to , including a photocopy of a valid identification and indicating the corresponding right to exercise.

## Language

In the event of discrepancies between the English and this version of the Terms and Conditions, the English version shall prevail.
